question_data = [
{"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]
question_data2 = [
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"Alaska is the largest state in the United States.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"Greenland is almost as big as Africa.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"History","question":"The United States was a member of the League of Nations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Board Games","question":"The Angry Video Game Nerd&#039;s alter ego is &quot;Board James&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Studies suggest that approximately 40% of the world population is left-handed.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]